<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Pyberry]]></title>
  <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-30T15:00:13-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Braxton Schafer]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bugfix: 1.0.1]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2014/01/30/bugfix-1-dot-0-1/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-30T14:42:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2014/01/30/bugfix-1-dot-0-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday I released version 1.0.1, which fixes some bugs I discovered while packaging and moves the config file and default database location to the proper application data directory.</p>

<p>This location is:
* C:\Users\$USERNAME\AppData\Local\Braxton Schafer\Pyberry on Windows
* /Users/$USERNAME/Library/Application Support/Pyberry on Mac
* /home/$USERNAME/.local/share/Pyberry on Linux</p>

<p>Additionally, there are packages available for Windows, Mac, and Linux, with no install necessary!  Just download from <a href="https://github.com/braxton-schafer/pyberry/releases/latest">here</a> and unzip.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Release: 1.0]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2014/01/28/major-release-1-dot-0/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-28T21:37:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2014/01/28/major-release-1-dot-0</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is it, I&rsquo;ve done it.  I&rsquo;ve tagged and pushed release 1.0.  I&rsquo;ve done as much testing as I can figure, but there&rsquo;s surely still bugs.  If you find a bug, please report it on <a href="https://github.com/braxton-schafer/pyberry/issues?state=open">GitHub</a> so I can fix it!</p>

<p>I also discovered the GitHub Releases feature, so I&rsquo;ll be phasing out the &ldquo;Downloads&rdquo; page of this website soon.</p>

<p>Download Pyberry 1.0 <a href="https://github.com/braxton-schafer/pyberry/releases/tag/1.0">here</a>.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m very excited for this huge milestone for me (it&rsquo;s my first project to hit 1.0/be reasonably stable), so I hope it benefits somebody else.  I&rsquo;m always open to feature requests or people looking to help.  You can find various ways to contact me at <a href="http://bjschafer.com">my website</a>, or just fork or open an issue on GitHub.</p>

<p>Thank you!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenLibrary and 0.10]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2014/01/22/openlibrary-and-0-dot-10/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-22T20:45:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2014/01/22/openlibrary-and-0-dot-10</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I was discovering a host of problems with the Google Books lookup, partially related to poor/inconsistent documentation.  So I made the decision to move to <a href="http://openlibrary.org">OpenLibrary</a> instead.  This necessitated a rewrite of much of the lookup code, and I took it as an opportunity to clean up and Pythonize a lot of the code relating to the lookup.</p>

<p>With this change, I decided to tag release 0.10.  Yeah, I&rsquo;m one of those people.  This change is certainly bigger than a bugfix but I&rsquo;m not yet comfortable releasing 1.0.  So after 9 comes 10&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bugfix: 0.9.1]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/10/25/bugfix-0-dot-9-1/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-25T11:59:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/10/25/bugfix-0-dot-9-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Due to a bug I discovered, I&rsquo;ve now released 0.9.1, which fixes a potential crash when looking up by title or ISBN.</p>

<p>It was possible, if the book didn&rsquo;t have an author attribute, for Pyberry to crash.  This is fixed in 0.9.1.</p>

<p>The release has been tagged in the git repo/GitHub, but I haven&rsquo;t packaged the release at this point.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pending Release: 1.0]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/10/23/pending-release-1-dot-0/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-23T13:29:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/10/23/pending-release-1-dot-0</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Pyberry is actually getting close to a 1.0 release!  This means that the features I wanted to see in it before it was released are implemented and it&rsquo;s tested so that it (hopefully) works well and robustly for all use cases.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s a feature freeze!  No new features will be implemented, only (hopefully minor) bug fixes!</p>

<p>Unfortunately, before we can actually release it, we need help testing!  That&rsquo;s where you come in.</p>

<h1>Requirements</h1>

<p>The only requirement is Google&rsquo;s <a href="https://code.google.com/p/google-api-python-client/"><code>google-api-python-client</code></a>.  After that, you should be able to clone it and test it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Site]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/10/23/new-site/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-23T12:13:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/10/23/new-site</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to Pyberry&rsquo;s new website!  It should make it simpler to update everybody on any changes as well as provide downloads and documentation.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backport Complete!]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/06/06/backport-complete/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/06/06/backport-complete</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I&#8217;ve just pushed version 0.4 of Pyberry to GitHub. &nbsp;It&#8217;s a biggie! &nbsp;I&#8217;ve backported it from Python 3 to Python 2.7 in order to use Google API modules. &nbsp;Because of that, I was able to make searching by title work. &nbsp;I&#8217;ve additionally cleaned up the code quite a bit, fixed bugs I found going through it, etc. &nbsp;Check out the new release <a href="https://github.com/braxton-schafer/pyberry/tree/0.4" target="_blank" title="GitHub!">here</a>, at GitHub. &nbsp;Now that I&#8217;ve pushed past the mega issue, I&#8217;m looking forward to ramping up development.<br /><br />I set a (probably unrealistic) due date for version 0.5 (basically, where most features should be there so that it&#8217;s purposeful) to be June 18, next Friday. &nbsp;I will work on it, but no guarantees about that milestone.<br /><br />By the way, I still (and always) need testers! &nbsp;If something doesn&#8217;t work, just open an issue on GitHub and I&#8217;ll do my best to fix it. &nbsp;This is very much a learning experience for me.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Py3k to Python 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/05/29/py3k-to-python-2/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-29T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/05/29/py3k-to-python-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Unfortunately, sometimes to move forward, you have to go backwards. &nbsp;In Pyberry, I&#8217;m in the process of moving all the code to Python 2, for library reasons. &nbsp;I&#8217;ve more than met my match in dealing with the data coming from the Google Books API, but Google provides a library to deal with it that&#8217;s Python 2.x only. &nbsp;So, I&#8217;ve decided to backport my code.<br /><br />More details to come - right now, I&#8217;m having issues finding decent documentation on the gdata-python libraries, but it&#8217;s still looking to be a lot easier.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for Release Specialist]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/02/21/looking-for-release-specialist/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/02/21/looking-for-release-specialist</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
The Pyberry project is looking for a Release Specialist - somebody who knows how to package versions for release cross-platform. &nbsp;Because Pyberry is written in Python, an interpreted language, it can run on many platforms. &nbsp;We&#8217;d like to at least have packages for Windows, Mac OS X and Linux so that a user on these platforms can simply install/run it without having to worry about downloading Python as well.<br /><br />If you would be willing to do this or help out in any other way, please let me know! &nbsp;Feel free to browse the code at <a href="https://sourceforge.net/p/pyberry/code/?branch=ref%2Fdevelop" target="_blank" title="Development branch">SourceForge</a>. &nbsp;If you&#8217;re interested, you can email me at <a href="mailto:braxton,schafer@users.sf.net" target="_blank">braxton.schafer@users.sf.net</a></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coming Soon in Pyberry 0.4]]></title>
    <link href="http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/02/21/coming-soon-in-pyberry-04/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://braxton-schafer.github.io/pyberry/blog/2013/02/21/coming-soon-in-pyberry-04</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Pyberry version 0.3 has been tagged for release but not packaged; you can get a copy of the source by doing a<br /><pre>git clone git://git.code.sf.net/p/pyberry/code pyberry-code</pre><br />I&#8217;d try to package it but as of now I don&#8217;t know anybody following development/interested in a newer version; feel free to leave a comment if you are and I&#8217;ll take some time to package it.<br /><br />I&#8217;ve instead been working on release 0.4, which will include the ability to add books by looking by something besides ISBN. &nbsp;I&#8217;m currently implementing add by title functionality but once that&#8217;s implemented more methods should follow easily and quickly.<br /><br />No timeframe because things come up and I know as soon as I give a timeframe I&#8217;ll miss it. &nbsp;Stay tuned for more updates.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
